questdiagnostics.com 2019-09-16

# Online Privacy Policy : Online Privacy Policy

**Quest Diagnostics Online Privacy Policy**

Quest Diagnostics and its wholly-owned subsidiaries (collectively "Quest Diagnostics") believe that privacy is important to the success and use of the Internet. This statement sets forth Quest Diagnostics policy and describes the practices that we will follow with respect to the privacy of the information of users of this site. Should you have any questions about this policy or our practices, please send an email to [Privacy@QuestDiagnostics.com](mailto:Privacy@QuestDiagnostics.com) or write to us at:

Quest Diagnostics   
Attention: Privacy Officer   
500 Plaza Drive   
Secaucus, NJ 07094

You can also call us at 800-222-0446, ext. 8954.

**What Personal Information We Collect**

Quest Diagnostics collects your personal information online when you voluntarily provide it to us. If you choose to register online, we ask you to provide limited personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number and/or email address. We also collect information that will allow you to establish a username and password if you would like to do that.

**How to Review and Change Your Personal Information**

If you register for a Quest Diagnostics account, you may review and change your personal information by [logging in to MyQuest](https://myquest.questdiagnostics.com/), then clicking on your name at the top of the screen and then clicking on “Manage Profile”, or by [logging into Billing](https://secure.questdiagnostics.com/PatientBilling/PatientBillingDef.action?fromLink=doPayment) and then clicking on “Manage My Account” and then “My Profile,” or by [logging in while making an Appointment](https://secure.questdiagnostics.com/hcp/psc/jsp/SearchLocation.do), then clicking on the “Cancel/Change/Confirm” link and then “Manage my Account”.

**How We Use Personal Information That We Collect Online**

Internal Uses

We may use your personal information within Quest Diagnostics: (1) to provide you with the services and products you request or that have been ordered and/or requested by your healthcare provider acting on your behalf; (2) to answer questions about our services; billing, payment methods or use of our website; (3) to process or collect payments for our services, (4) to conduct customer surveys; and (5) to contact you about the products and services that we offer.

Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

We will not disclose any personal information to any third party (excluding our contractors to whom we may provide such information for the limited purpose of providing services to us and who are obligated to keep the information confidential), unless (1) you have authorized us to do so; (2) we are legally required to do so, for example, in response to a subpoena, court order or other legal process and/or, (3) it is necessary to protect our property rights related to this website. We also may share aggregate, non-personal information about website usage with unaffiliated third parties. This aggregate information does not contain any personal information about our users.

**Cookie Placement**

Certain Quest Diagnostics websites, like many other commercial sites, may use a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how our site is used. Cookies were designed to help a website operator determine that a particular user had visited the site previously and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set. We may use cookies to keep track of information about your current web browsing session which will be discarded as soon as you log out or close your web browser. This information also allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our site and for what purpose. We may also make use of “persistent or memory based” cookies, which remain on your computer’s hard drive until you delete them. Examples include our use of these cookies to pre-populate forms you complete on our website based on information you have previously provided to us, enable interest-based advertising and collect information about your web browsing history. Although you have the ability to modify your browser to either accept all cookies, notify you when a cookie is sent, or reject all cookies, it may not be possible to utilize our services if you reject cookies.

Quest Diagnostics uses the services of Google Analytics, and may use other similar services, to collect and analyze statistical data about visitors to our website. We also use Google advertising services, including a remarketing function, and may use other similar services, to arrange for you to see Quest Diagnostics advertisements when you visit certain third party websites. These analytic and advertising services do not collect personally identifiable information. You may elect to opt out of the use of non-personally identifiable data by Google Analytics by downloading and installing an add-on to your web browser found [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). You may find out more about how Google Analytics collects and processes data by visiting “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps,” found [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You may also opt out of the Google AdWords service we use to serve ads, and which service also collects non-personally identifiable information, by visiting the Google Ad Settings page [here](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en).

**How We Protect Information Online**

We exercise great care to protect your personal information. This includes, among other things, using industry standard techniques such as firewalls, encryption, and intrusion detection. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us. This is especially true for information you transmit to us via email since we have no way of protecting that information until it reaches us since email does not have the security features that are built into our websites.

In addition, we limit Quest Diagnostics' employees and contractors' access to personal information. Only those employees and contractors with a business reason to know have access to this information. We educate our employees about the importance of maintaining confidentiality of customer information.

We review our security arrangements from time to time as we deem appropriate.

**How can you help protect your information?**

If you are using a Quest Diagnostics website for which you registered and choose a password, we recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of the Quest Diagnostics website and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if others have access to your computer.  

**E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework**

As further described in our [Privacy Shield Notice](/home/privacy-policy/privacy-shield.html), Quest Diagnostics and some of our U.S.-based affiliated companies have certified to and comply with the E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. The Privacy Shield principles are: Notice; Choice (Consent); Accountability for Onward Transfer; Security; Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation; Access; and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. For more information on the E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield or to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov>.  

**Links to Other Sites**

We want to provide site visitors valuable information, services and products. Featured programs and other site content within the Quest Diagnostics site may link our users to third party sites. Quest Diagnostics does not control and is not responsible for practices of any third-party websites.

**Note**

From time to time, we may change this privacy statement. For example, as we update and improve our services, new features may require modifications to the privacy statement. Accordingly, please check back periodically.

Non-Discrimination Notice

Quest Diagnostics Incorporated and its subsidiaries (Quest Diagnostics) complies with applicable Federal civil rights laws and does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, national origin, age, disability, or sex. Quest Diagnostics does not exclude people or treat them differently because of race, color, national origin, age, disability, or sex.

Quest Diagnostics:

  * Provides language services free of charge to people whose primary language is not English, such as: 
    * Qualified interpreters
  * Provides aids and services free of charge to people with disabilities to communicate effectively with us, such as: 
    * Auxiliary aids and services
    * Written information in other formats (audio, accessible electronic formats, other formats)

If you need these services, contact 1.844.698.1022 or ask at a Quest Diagnostics patient service center.

If you believe that Quest Diagnostics has failed to provide these services or discriminated in another way on the basis of race, color, national origin, age, disability, or sex, you can file a grievance with:

Quest Diagnostics  
Civil Rights Coordinator   
1201 S. Collegeville Road  
Collegeville, PA 19426  
1.800.420.7225  
PatientAdvocacy@QuestDiagnostics.com.

You can file a grievance in person or by mail, fax, or email. If you need help filing a grievance, the Quest Diagnostics Civil Rights Coordinator is available to help you.

You can also file a civil rights complaint with the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services, Office for Civil Rights, electronically through the Office for Civil Rights Complaint Portal, available at https://ocrportal.hhs.gov/ocr/portal/lobby.jsf, or by mail or phone at:

U.S. Department of Health and Human Services  
200 Independence Avenue, SW  
Room 509F, HHH Building  
Washington, D.C. 20201  
1.800.368.1019, 800.537.7697 (TDD)

Language Assistance Services

ATTENTION: If you speak English, language assistance services, free of charge, are available to you. Call 1.844.698.1022.

ATENCIÓN: si habla Español (Spanish), tiene a su disposición servicios gratuitos de asistencia lingüística. Llame al 1.844.698.1022.

注意：如果您使用繁體中文(Chinese), 您可以免費獲得語言援助服務。請致電1.844.698.1022。

ATTENTION : Si vous parlez Français(French), des services d'aide linguistique vous sont proposés gratuitement. Appelez le 1.844.698.1022.

ATANSYON: Si w pale Kreyòl Ayisyen(French Creole), gen sèvis èd pou lang ki disponib gratis pou ou. Rele 1.844.698.1022.

PAUNAWA: Kung nagsasalita ka ng Tagalog(Tagalog), maaari kang gumamit ng mga serbisyo ng tulong sa wika nang walang bayad. Tumawag sa 1.844.698.1022.

CHÚ Ý: Nếu bạn nói Tiếng Việt(Vietnamese), có các dịch vụ hỗ trợ ngôn ngữ miễn phí dành cho bạn. Gọi số 1.844.698.1022.

주의: 한국어(Korean)를 사용하시는 경우, 언어 지원 서비스를 무료로 이용하실 수 있습니다. 1.844.698.1022 번으로 전화해 주십시오.

ACHTUNG: Wenn Sie Deutsch(German) sprechen, stehen Ihnen kostenlos sprachliche Hilfsdienstleistungen zur Verfügung. Rufnummer: 1.844.698.1022.

ملحوظة: إذا كنت تتحدث اذكر(Arabic) اللغة، فإن خدمات المساعدة اللغوية تتوافر لك بالمجان. اتصل برقم 1.844.698.1022.

ВНИМАНИЕ: Если вы говорите на Pусском(Russian) языке, то вам доступны бесплатные услуги перевода. Звоните 1.844.698.1022.

ATTENZIONE: In caso la lingua parlata sia l'Italiano(Italian), sono disponibili servizi di assistenza linguistica gratuiti. Chiamare il numero 1.844.698.1022.

ATENÇÃO: Se fala Português(Portuguese), encontram-se disponíveis serviços linguísticos, grátis. Ligue para 1.844.698.1022.

ध्यान दें: यदि आप हिंदी(Hindi) बोलते हैं तो आपके लिए मुफ्त में भाषा सहायता सेवाएं उपलब्ध हैं। 1.844.698.1022 पर कॉल करें।

UWAGA: Jeżeli mówisz po Polsku(Polish), możesz skorzystać z bezpłatnej pomocy językowej. Zadzwoń pod numer 1.844.698.1022.

注意事項：日本語(Japanese)を話される場合、無料の言語支援をご利用いただけます。1.844.698.1022 まで、お電話にてご連絡ください。

Date: December 5, 2018    

Top of Page
